leadmaverick.com 2013-09-15

# Lead Maverick Privacy Policy

**Updated on Thursday, April 26, 2007**   
Please note that the practices of Lead Maverick, Inc, its affiliates, and agents ("Lead Maverick"), with respect to personal information, are now governed by this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time, and not the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the personal information was collected. We encourage users to regularly review our Privacy Policy. Also see changes in sections entitled "Collection of personal information" and "Your choices with respect to personal information." To update your information and preferences, see the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences." 

This document sets forth the Lead Maverick Online Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") for this website, [www.LeadMaverick.com](http://www.leadmaverick.com/) and the Lead Maverick application (application.leadmaverick.com) (collectively, the “Site”). If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities or other Lead Maverick websites, except as expressly set forth in the section entitled "Data not collected on this site." 

**Changes in Privacy Policy**   
All personal information ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains and that is NOT identified as PUBLIC Information) that we collect and maintain will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. Lead Maverick reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and will provide notice of material changes on the home page of the Site. If as the result of such changes, you want to alter the ways in which Lead Maverick is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described in the section entitled “Updating your personal information and privacy preferences.” You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy after such notice has been posted with the following exception: If at the time you provide personal information to Lead Maverick you are given the opportunity (as you currently are) to limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by Lead Maverick or by third parties, Lead Maverick will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent. However, if Lead Maverick sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or Lead Maverick (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by or merged with another entity, Lead Maverick may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without your consent, but Lead Maverick will provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on this Site. 

**Entities collecting personal information  
** Personal information on this Site is collected by Lead Maverick. Lead Maverick, Inc, 16775 Addison Road, Suite 100, Addison, Texas 75001 and its telephone number is 214-704-2144. 

The Site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.

**Updating your personal information and privacy preferences**   
You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. With respect to Registration Information (as defined in the section entitled "Protection of your personal information"), this may be accomplished by linking to your account at My Account, where you can view and make changes to your personal information along with your public information. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications from Lead Maverick or third parties) by writing or calling Lead Maverick at: 

Lead Maverick, Inc   
16775 Addison Road   
Suite 100   
Addison, TX 75001   
Telephone number: 214-704-2144 

Please include your name, address, and/or e-mail address when you contact us.

Personal information submitted through this Site that is not Registration Information is not accessible online. To access and/or correct such information, you may write Lead Maverick at:

Lead Maverick, Inc    
16775 Addison Road, Suite 100   
Addison, Texas 75001   
USA 

In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site where you provided your personal information. You should expect a response within 30 days. 

**Collection of personal information  
** As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing online software applications, Lead Maverick may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, Lead Maverick may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information. When ordering products or services on the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. 

When you use the Site, Lead Maverick or third parties authorized by Lead Maverick may also collect certain technical and routing information about your computer to facilitate your use of the Site and its services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. We use these environmental variables to facilitate and track your use of the Site and its services. Lead Maverick also uses such environmental variables to measure traffic patterns on the Site. Without expressly informing you in each particular circumstance, we do not match such information with any of your personal information. 

When you submit personal information to Lead Maverick through the Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in any of the countries in which Lead Maverick maintains offices including, without limitation, the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted vendors of Lead Maverick. Such vendors are bound by contract not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties. One instance where this could occur is in conjunction with framed pages in which the URL for the pages is not visible, and the pages are being hosted by a vendor of Lead Maverick.

Lead Maverick has established relationships with various service providers whose services are available to you from the Site or from websites that are linked to the Site. Typically, these providers offer services that Lead Maverick customers might find useful, such as those that can be used in conjunction with Lead Maverick services and products. In order to use those services, you may be required to provide personal information to the providers. Unless expressly provided to the contrary, personal information that you provide while you are visiting a provider's website will be subject to the privacy policy posted on such site, and personal information that you provide while on the Site in conjunction with a provider's service will be subject to this Privacy Policy. You should be aware that our agreements with these service providers often provide that they will share with Lead Maverick personal information collected from you. In such instances, Lead Maverick may use this information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. In the situation where sites have an Lead Maverick "look and feel" and you reasonably believe you are on an Lead Maverick site, the site is collecting information in a solely intermediary capacity and does not use personal information for secondary purposes.

In order to reduce errors in our database, authenticate our users, and prevent abuse of our system, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submit to us with information from third-party sources. For example, we may supplement your Registration Information with address information provided by the U.S. Postal Service to qualify your information and prevent errors in our database. As permissible, we may also supplement the information you provide to us with demographic and other information (such as age or interest in photography) stored in third-party databases in order to make it more likely that marketing communications we send will be of interest to you.

**How your personal information is used  
** Lead Maverick collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the activities you select. If you subscribe to a service or register a product, for example, the information is used to register your rights, if any, to technical support or other benefits that may be made available to registered users. As another example, if you enter a contest, information is collected to qualify the entry and to contact you regarding the contest or prize awards. Your personal information is also used to track customer preferences and keep you informed about product upgrades, special offers, and other products and services of Lead Maverick and selected third parties unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such communications are prohibited by law. 

Lead Maverick may collect information about the use of the Site, such as the types of services used and how many users we receive daily. This information is collected in aggregate form, without identifying any user individually. Lead Maverick may use this aggregate, nonidentifying statistical data for statistical analysis, marketing, or similar promotional purposes.

**Your choices with respect to personal information**   
Lead Maverick recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on the Site. Lead Maverick may communicate information to you regarding products, services, and special offers available from Lead Maverick or selected third parties unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such communications are prohibited by law, although we may find it necessary to communicate with you regarding your use of the services on the Site. Except in the particular circumstances described in this Privacy Policy, Lead Maverick will also not provide your name to other companies or organizations without your consent. 

There are other instances in which Lead Maverick may divulge your personal information, such as where required by law, regulation, or litigation. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.

**Protection of your personal information**   
The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of Lead Maverick products or services or registering an Lead Maverick product is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Registration Information resides on a secure server that only selected Lead Maverick personnel and contractors have access to via password. Lead Maverick encrypts your personal information and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information when it is transmitted to Lead Maverick. 

Personal information that you provide that does not constitute Registration Information also resides on a secure server and is accessible only to selected Lead Maverick personnel and contractors via password. Since this information is not accessible by you, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.

Please note that any information you post to a public bulletin board or public website, in the case of Lead Maverick content, is available to all persons accessing that location.  Your e-mail address would then be available to all persons accessing the website. In addition, you should be aware that the Lead Maverick application and websites offer a service in which subscribers are e-mailed a copy of all messages posted. 

**Data not collected on this Site  
** Personal information that is not collected on the Site is not generally subject to this Privacy Policy. However, personal information submitted on physical product registration cards is classified as Registration Information and is subject to this Privacy Policy. If you wish to access and/or correct such information, please see instructions for doing so in the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences." 

**Use of cookies  
** When you visit this Site, you can browse the Site and access important information without revealing your identity. In order to improve our Site, we and our vendors use "cookies" to track your visit. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. It functions as your identification card and enables Lead Maverick to record your passwords, purchases, and preferences. It cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. 

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies will probably not be able to access those pages.)

While Lead Maverick and our vendors use cookies to track your visit to the Site, and our web servers automatically log the IP/Internet address of your computer, Lead Maverick does not generally use this information to identify you personally. However, if you expressly provide consent for the Site to "remember" the unique identifier that you select when you register for various activities on the Site, that unique identifier will be stored on a cookie on your computer, linked to your Registration Information, and your navigation path around the Site will be tracked. We associate this data to understand how our Site and services are being used so we can understand our customers and offer appropriate products and services.

**Privacy complaints  
** Lead Maverick takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that Lead Maverick has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write the Lead Maverick Privacy Officer at the following address or fill out a privacy complaint form: 

**Privacy Officer/Customer Information**   
Lead Maverick, Inc    
16775 Addison Road, Suite 100   
Addison, Texas 75001   
USA 

In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Lead Maverick Online Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. 

If you provide Lead Maverick with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion that they may not), Lead Maverick will endeavor to update your privacy preferences in a timely and accurate manner.

Also, please note that Lead Maverick is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non Lead Maverick websites to which this Site or any other Lead Maverick website may link. You should review the privacy policy of such sites before using the sites.
